VIDEO EDITOR

EDITING REEL https://tinyurl.com/AJacobsEditingReel

EDUCATION

B.F.A. Film Production | Editing Chapman University 2018-2022 4.0 GPA Minor in Visual Journalism Presidential Scholar, Dean's List

University of Cape Town Semester Study Abroad, Spring 2020

SKILLS

Avid Media Composer Adobe Premiere Davinci Resolve Adobe After Effects Adobe Photoshop **Protools** Microsoft Office Digital photography















linkedin.com/in/aleiajacobs/

ALEIA JACOBS

503-530-6068 aljacobs@chapman.edu aleiajacobs.com

SUMMARY

Passionate editor and film student bringing experience from editing ten student films, working on over twenty sets, and interning internationally with two production companies. Dedicated to collaborating with the key crew to support their creative visions. Efficient and self-motivated with an aptitude for handling strict deadlines and multitasking.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Assistant Editor Intern | Dirt Merchant Films

04/2020 - Present

Los Angeles, CA

Work in post-production providing notes, editing, and research on multiple independent films

Production Intern | TinToy Productions

02/2020 - 03/2020

Cape Town, South Africa

Internship cut short due to COVID-19

Aided in post production workflow and provided assistance on set Learned the entire workflow from pre to post production of a boutique production company

Shift Manager | Handel's Homemade Ice Cream and Yogurt Sherwood, OR

06/2017 - 01/2020

Supervised the actions of up to six staff members at one time Trained all new employees

Performed closing duties with the till such as counting money, depositing earnings, and transcribing records

Served customers and produced pre-packaged products to sell

STUDENT FILM PROJECTS

EDITOR

How to Kill a Cowboy (2019-Present)

Gnarly (2019-2020)

Luz (2019)

My House (2019)

Waldo the Plumber (2019)

Boiling Point (2019)

Phantom Blonde (2019)

Room for Rent Episodes 1-3 (2019)

Official selection for 2019 LA Shorts International Film Festival

OTHER ROLES

Luz (Writer, Director)

My House (DIT, Script Supervisor)

Foundation (2nd Assistant Director)

Waldo the Plumber (Production Designer, Script Supervisor)

Boiling Point (1st Assistant Director, DIT)

Phantom Blonde (Script Supervisor)

Room for Rent Episodes 1-3 (Sound Designer)

Hot Wheelz (Sound Mixer)

Mr. Pervy Wilkins (Best Boy Grip)

Assembly Required (1st Assistant Camera, 2nd Assistant Camera)

Home for the Summer (Best Boy Electric)

Bloom (Best Boy Grip)